thanks everybody for coming I know it's
谢谢大家的光临，我知道
late in the day and the party's tonight
在一天的深夜和聚会的今晚
I really appreciate you guys coming in
我真的很感谢你们的到来
rich and I certainly appreciate it we've
有钱，我当然很感谢我们
got a Raspberry Pi up here if you want
如果需要的话，可以在这里买一台Raspberry Pi
to take a look at it and then an
看看它，然后
application that visualizes actually
实际可视化的应用程序
supposed to visualize the data off the
应该将数据可视化
Raspberry Pi but we're not getting a
树莓派，但我们没有得到
signal through this giant Faraday cage
通过巨大的法拉第笼发出的信号
that is the building anyways this is
那是建筑物，这是
visualizing air traffic data with the
通过可视化空中交通数据
FAA satellite based surveillance system
基于FAA卫星的监视系统
and Raspberry Pi so the goal today here
和Raspberry Pi，所以今天的目标是
is just a very short spiel about what we
只是关于我们的简短讲话
do we're going to talk about innovation
我们要谈论创新吗
and disruption and how IOT is growing
和破坏以及物联网如何增长
very fast and then we're going to go
非常快，然后我们要去
into a very specific use case around the
围绕着一个非常具体的用例
Raspberry Pi for air traffic control
Raspberry Pi用于空中交通管制
data but there are many other use cases
数据，但还有许多其他用例
this is just a great inexpensive end
这只是一个很棒的便宜的目的
point and this solution could be used
点，可以使用此解决方案
over and over again for many different
一遍又一遍地为许多不同
types of use cases we'll go through all
所有类型的用例类型
the components that I assembled this is
我组装的组件是
a little bit more refined there's a nice
稍微精致一点
case that comes with this one but you'll
附带的保护套，但您会
see originally I had a pizza box and and
最初看到我有一个披萨盒，然后
then rich will talk about the will do
然后有钱人会谈论意志
with the demo and rich will talk about
与演示和丰富将谈论
the future of IOT and disruption and
物联网和破坏的未来
innovation briefly so we're giving away
短暂地创新，所以我们放弃了
a book Kindle version of this book this
本书的Kindle版本
is the Oracle cloud book that we've
是我们所拥有的Oracle云书
recently updated with over 100 pages if
最近更新的页面超过100页，如果
you want it be entered into the drawing
您希望将其输入到工程图中
just email hello at viscosity na komm
只需通过粘度na komm向您问好
and we'll get you entered into the
我们会带您进入
drawing I'll give you a secret if you
绘画，如果你愿意，我会给你一个秘密
send us an email we'll send you a free
给我们发送电子邮件，我们将免费为您发送
copy of the book you can download it on
该书的副本可以下载到
Amazon and it's always being updated
亚马逊，并且一直在更新
Oracle changes their cloud screens every
Oracle每次都会更改其云屏幕
every couple of weeks so we're keeping
每两周，所以我们保持
it updated if you want to get in this
如果您要进入此更新
drawing yep
是的
and you put in a card in the bag the
然后你把卡片放在袋子里
Jeff ticks around then we'll put in the
杰夫四处走动，然后我们将
drawing and if you're here when we pull
绘图，如果您在这里，当我们拉
your name then you win good hot cool
你的名字，然后你会赢得好热酷
not everybody has a card if you write
如果写的话，不是每个人都有一张卡
your name email on it sure you could
您的姓名电子邮件肯定会
take a card and write your email on it
拿一张卡并在上面写你的电子邮件
if you want do you want to get the
如果你想得到
drawing
画画
oh that's Hello at viscosity North
哦，粘度北您好
America na komm yeah I'll have another
America na komm是的，我还要
slide at the end we'll just send you a
幻灯片的结尾，我们将仅向您发送
code for a Kindle book and then that'll
Kindle书的代码，然后
just keep it updated use their reader so
只是保持更新使用他们的读者，所以
a little bit about me I'm from Austin
关于我的一些事我来自奥斯丁
Texas I'm an engineer and developer
德州我是一名工程师和开发人员
those are my twitter handles I got
这些是我得到的推特手柄
involved with apex quite a few years ago
几年前涉足先端
I really liked it as a low code platform
我真的很喜欢它作为低代码平台
before we really had a word for that I'm
在我们真的有一个词之前，我是
co-author of that Oracle cloud solution
该Oracle云解决方案的合著者
guys that were given away and I'm a
那些被赠送的家伙，我是
co-founder with rich anaemic of
富有贫血的联合创始人
viscosity in North America I'm also a
在北美的粘度我也是
private pilot which is why this subject
私人飞行员，这就是为什么这个主题
is very interesting to me and I have a
对我来说很有趣，我有一个
passion for the red grape my wife and I
对我和我妻子的红葡萄的热情
have a very small vineyard in Argentina
在阿根廷有一个很小的葡萄园
where we run Oracle and pick grapes and
我们在哪里运行Oracle并采摘葡萄和
make some wine and so viscosity this
做一些酒，所以粘度
year we we will have by the end of the
年底，我们将拥有
year have given more than 100
一年给了一百多
presentations around the country and
全国各地的演讲
worldwide we give presentations through
在全球范围内，我们通过
Latin America Australia New Zealand
拉丁美洲澳大利亚新西兰
Europe rich has been to China India UK
欧洲富人去过中国印度英国
so just and and we're only about 50
所以我们只有大约50
people in our company so it's just it's
公司里的人，就是这样
one of the things we really care about
我们真正关心的一件事
and it's
这是
it's something that we do to try to give
这是我们要做的尝试
back so at the core of viscosity is a
回到所以粘度的核心是
very robust data visualization
非常强大的数据可视化
predictive prescriptive analytics
预测性规范分析
application development practice you can
您可以进行应用程序开发实践
engage us for assessments proof of
聘请我们进行评估证明
concepts training full-blown projects
培训成熟项目的概念
and manage services and we do pretty
和管理服务，我们做得很漂亮
much the entire read stack and quite a
整个读取堆栈，而且相当
bit of things outside of Oracle as well
Oracle之外的一些事情
just a sampling of some of our clients
只是我们一些客户的样本
we believe in innovation and innovation
我们相信创新和创新
we think is necessary for businesses to
我们认为企业必须
survive especially now and we've also
特别是现在生存，我们也
written over a dozen books on data the
写了十几本关于数据的书
cloud and Oracle including rich has a
云和甲骨文（包括富人）拥有
book the Oracle 12c performance tuning
预定Oracle 12c性能调优
it's the best-selling book and Oracle
这是畅销书和Oracle
press turn it over to rich and he's
按把它变成富有，他是
going to talk he's gonna level set us
要谈他将要设置水平
with IOT so why do you need to innovate
与物联网，为什么你需要创新
Peter Drucker said it best the
彼得·德鲁克（Peter Drucker）说最好
enterprise that that does not innovate
不创新的企业
ages and declines and in a period of
年龄和衰落，并在
rapid change such as the present that
诸如现在这样的快速变化
decline will be fast so I always like to
下降会很快，所以我一直喜欢
say take Lou Holtz Lou Holtz always says
说走Lou Holtz总是说Lou Holtz
you want to win later remember win
你想赢了以后记得赢
what's important now I think what's
现在重要的是我认为
important now is start to learn those
现在重要的是开始学习那些
pieces of what you can build you're
您可以建立的部分是
gonna see one half you can build but you
会看到一半你可以建造，但是你
can build anything your mind can think
可以建立您的思维能力
of and that's the key to this how many
这就是这多少的关键
people are familiar with this Gartner
人们对Gartner很熟悉
hype cycle this is like coming up this
炒作周期这就像来这
side here it's like these are things
这边就像这些东西
coming on these are things you're so
来吧，这些都是你如此
sick they're talking about them forever
生病了，他们一直在谈论他们
you want them to shut up about them
你想让他们闭嘴
they're overhyped and it kind of goes
他们被过度炒作了
down I don't know if that's ever going
下来，我不知道那会不会
to take off that BAM it takes off and
脱掉它的BAM
people are actually using it and how
人们实际上正在使用它，以及如何
many years it takes to go through this
这需要很多年
hype cycle is based on the color of the
炒作周期基于颜色
thing so something like quantum computer
诸如量子计算机之类的东西
is going to take
将采取
more than 10 years so you could see in
超过10年，所以您可以看到
2013 was kind of all about tech you know
2013年是您所了解的全部技术领域
big data predictive analytics the cloud
大数据预测分析云
to some degree if you look at innovation
在某种程度上，如果你看创新
and how you're really going to make that
以及您如何真正做到这一点
impact your innovation is something new
影响您的创新是新事物
you look at companies today and Wall
你看今天的公司和沃尔
Street will back a company to wipe out a
街将支持公司消灭
company that's been in business for 50
营业了50年的公司
years why because the company that's
年为什么，因为那家公司
been in business for 50 years doesn't
经营了50年没有
innovate they stay in the past they
创新他们留在过去
don't leverage technology they don't
不要利用他们没有的技术
leverage big data they don't leverage
利用他们不利用的大数据
internet of things they don't leverage
他们没有利用的物联网
robotics and what happens is let's say
机器人技术和发生的事情可以说
you invented the Telegraph way back when
您发明电报的方式可以追溯到
it's picking up people start buying it
人们开始购买它
now tons of people are buying it and
现在有很多人在购买它，
then all a sudden nobody's buying it why
然后突然没有人买它，为什么
because maybe the phone came out some
因为也许电话出来了
new technology passes it up you always
新技术总是让您流连忘返
have to be able to say what's important
必须能够说出什么是重要的
now is to be able to realize what
现在要能够意识到
technology is gone it's the Telegraph
技术不见了，这是电报
and what's the new technology the
什么是新技术
telephone no matter how much money you
电话不管你多少钱
put in these old companies will put in
放在这些老公司里
all kinds of investment in the old
各种旧投资
product and it doesn't lead lead to very
产品，它不会导致导致
little we saw a postal mail also there's
很少我们看到邮政邮件
a lot of email doesn't mean there isn't
很多电子邮件并不意味着没有
postal mail it's still there there's
邮政邮件仍然在那里
probably people are saying I told you a
可能有人说我告诉过你一个
mail wouldn't be big look at postal mail
邮件在邮政邮件中不会显得太大
still doing great a telegraph went to
仍然做得很好，电报去了
the telephone I remember my son seeing a
我记得我儿子在电话里看到
dictionary he was leaving college and
他要离开大学的字典，
somebody had thrown one out and he's
有人扔了一个，他是
looking at it like it's an Egyptian
像埃及人一样看着它
artifact I'm like what it what is it
神器，我喜欢它是什么
he's like it's a dictionary an actual
他就像是一本字典
one he's like who would ever use one and
他就像一个会用一个
I'm like well it's not used so I guess
我很好，它没有用过，所以我猜
nobody now it's going faster email I'm
现在没有人，我的电子邮件速度更快
going to snapchat Instagram people send
要去Instagram的人发送的snapchat
you a picture you know you don't know
你一张照片你知道你不知道
what it is they don't care right can you
他们不在乎是什么，对吗
keep up USB is not in the cloud I
跟上USB不在云中
remember my daughter saying what are you
记得我女儿说你是什么
carrying a USB for and I'm like why so I
带有USB的，我很想为什么我
can move the file from here to here
可以将文件从这里移动到这里
she's like why now why would you ever do
她就像为什么现在为什么你会做
that that's idiotic
那是白痴
and I'm like well that's Microsoft
我很好，那就是微软
PowerPoint and you got to move to
PowerPoint，您必须转到
another computer that has PowerPoint
另一台装有PowerPoint的计算机
they have paid for it on that computer
他们已经在那台计算机上付款了
too
太
you're gonna carry it somewhere else
你会把它带到其他地方
you're gonna carry it everywhere how
你会随身携带它
stupid is that I thought you were smart
愚蠢的是我以为你很聪明
but it's starting to move to where if
但是它开始移动到如果
it's gonna go to implants robotics first
首先要去植入机器人
it's being implanted in a robot but
它被植入机器人中
pretty soon it'll be implanted in you
很快它将被植入您体内
you know the computer was on your desk
你知道电脑在你的桌子上
then it was in your pocket and it's on
然后就在你的口袋里，就在
your wrist next thing is gonna go on
你的手腕接下来会发生
your wrist it's coming Google why are
你的手腕来了Google为什么
they so successful because they're big
他们如此成功，因为他们很大
on innovation ideas come from everywhere
关于创新的想法无处不在
they realize it's not just the top guy
他们意识到这不只是顶尖人物
who has the best ideas focus on data not
谁拥有最好的主意而不是数据
politics
政治
sorry innovation not instant perfection
遗憾的创新不是即时的完美
creativity loves restraint I don't know
创造力爱克制，我不知道
about that one IOT coming fast you're
关于一个物联网快速发展的事实
looking at it right here it's right on
看着它就在这里
the desk you could build anything
桌子上你可以建任何东西
Jerry's gonna show you how I ot inside a
杰瑞（Jerry）会告诉你我如何
manufacturing plan machines just talking
制造计划机只是在说
to machines they don't need to talk to a
到他们不需要与机器对话的机器
person you see it in all kinds of
您看到的各种人
devices in the consumer area whether
消费领域的设备是否
it's wearables video audio in your home
这是您家中的可穿戴视频音频
this one the baby one that baby moves
这是婴儿移动的婴儿之一
the bottle starts to warm up so when the
瓶子开始变热，所以当
baby cries the bottles already warm this
婴儿哭了已经温暖的瓶子
one is like a refrigerator tied to your
一个就像冰箱绑在你的
bathroom scale so it's like you know
浴室磅秤，就像你知道的
we're not going to unlock the
我们不会解锁
refrigerator until you buy more of this
冰箱，直到你买更多
stuff there's a tight button IOT right
东西有一个紧的按钮物联网吧
on your washing machine you press it you
在洗衣机上按一下
get tied you got a four-year-old you're
被绑，你有一个四岁的你
getting it a lot of tide and they know
得到很多潮汐，他们知道
that so they give you a Doritos button
这样他们给您一个Doritos按钮
now press the Doritos button that's a
现在按下Doritos按钮
little better
好一点
no we'll just give you a LexA and the
不，我们只会给您LexA，
little kid can say Alexa send some
小孩可以说Alexa发送一些
Doritos how much
多力多滋多少
a truckload you know it's coming
一卡车，你知道它要来了
tracking animals with IOT they're
用物联网追踪动物
tracking you with IOT there's a little
用物联网跟踪您，有一点
sensor in your shopping cart you know
您知道购物车中的传感器
here rich went around he bought some
富人在这里转转，他买了一些
milk circled the Oreo cookies multiple
牛奶盘绕着奥利奥饼干多个
times didn't buy any why because Tec was
时代不买任何原因，因为Tec是
you know distracted so think about
你知道分心所以想一想
disruptive type of innovation how you
破坏性的创新方式
disrupt your own company with innovation
通过创新破坏自己的公司
it passes something else go after the
它通过了别的之后
low-level people first doesn't use a lot
低水平的人首先不使用很多
of what you have then start going after
然后你开始追求
the higher ones but leverage big data
较高的但利用大数据
IOT robotics let's see one way how to do
物联网机器人技术让我们看看一种方法
it with Gerry thanks rich
与格里一起感谢富人
so I just want to play this is a video
所以我只想播放这是一个视频
that went viral on YouTube and it has a
在YouTube上风靡一时，
really well done visualization just to
做得很好的可视化
give you an idea of what air traffic
让您了解空中交通的状况
looks like is there any sound it should
看起来应该有声音吗
be yeah
是的
so early morning we have this whole
所以清晨我们有整个
train of airplanes coming from the US
来自美国的飞机火车
right over to London
就在伦敦
and it start to gets busier you can see
它开始变得更忙，您可以看到
them be routed into holding patterns
他们被路由到等待模式
that sort of thing
之类的东西
look at these guys those are military
看看这些家伙，他们是军人
planes right
飞机右
so the way they track this is all this
所以他们追踪的方式就是全部
data is collected sent out by the
数据收集由
aircraft I'm sorry these are the
飞机，对不起，这些是
military planes yeah
军用飞机
sent out by these aircraft and they
由这些飞机发出，他们
visualize it in three-dimensional space
在三维空间中可视化
these are a lot of helicopters going out
这些是很多直升飞机
to the offshore drilling platforms out
到海上钻井平台出来
of in the in the North Atlantic
在北大西洋
[Music]
[音乐]
so anyway so how does this work so we
所以无论如何，这是如何工作的，所以我们
use two systems we use what's called the
使用两个系统，我们使用所谓的
ATSB
ATSB
air traffic control system and this is a
空中交通管制系统，这是一个
ship-to-ship communication that's
船对船的沟通
installed in aircraft and it's actually
安装在飞机上，实际上
mandated to take effect in even the
授权甚至在
smallest aircraft within the next year
明年内最小的飞机
and they've also released the same
他们也发布了相同的
technology in two satellites so there
技术在两颗卫星中
was some dead spots over the Atlantic
在大西洋上空有些死角
but basically ground station ground
但基本上是地面站地面
radar contract planes that used to be
曾经是
the only way to track planes and now the
跟踪飞机的唯一方法，现在
planes since they have very accurate GPS
飞机，因为它们具有非常精确的GPS
and radios and they can transmit their
和收音机，他们可以传输他们的
locations to other planes and to ground
其他飞机和地面的位置
stations ground stations can also track
地面站也可以跟踪
aircraft that don't have any signals and
没有任何信号的飞机
then relay that through the system and
然后通过系统中继
we're listening to that signal here with
我们在这里听那个信号
the Raspberry Pi unfortunately I can't
不幸的是，Raspberry Pi无法
get a signal through this room but we
通过这个房间收到信号，但是我们
did pre record some data that will show
是否预先记录了一些将显示的数据
you so how do you assemble this yourself
你，你怎么自己组装
it's it's it's not expensive right I
是的，这不贵吧
mean the Raspberry Pi is a $30 computer
表示Raspberry Pi是一台价值30美元的计算机
we bought two radios both 1090 megahertz
我们买了两台1090兆赫的收音机
and 978 megahertz an 8 gig micro SD
和978兆赫的8 gig micro SD
memory card battery and some
存储卡电池和一些
miscellaneous cables and you can put
杂项电缆，你可以把
this whole solution together at the time
当时整个解决方案
I did this a few years ago that you had
我几年前做过的
to do this yourself with
自己做
software-defined radios and that sort of
软件定义的无线电以及诸如此类的
thing but now you can buy the completed
东西，但现在您可以购买完成的
kits for less than $100 and one of the
售价不到$ 100的套件，其中之一
easiest ways to get going is to simply
最简单的方法就是
download the image from Stratos has been
从Stratos下载图像已
packaged up and they have you know
包装，他们有你知道
single band for a $94 dual band and then
94美元的双乐队，然后
they can just send you all the parts you
他们可以将所有零件发送给您
even get a nice case and then go
甚至得到一个很好的案例，然后去
download the software the current
下载当前软件
version off of github and this guy named
版本从github和这个家伙命名
Chris Young gave it to us so thanks for
克里斯·扬（Chris Young）给了我们，谢谢
him and then
他然后
it capitalizes on a piece of software
它利用了一个软件
called dump 1090 that was written by
称为转储1090，由
this guy sent salvador Sanfilippo kind
这家伙送萨尔瓦多·桑菲利波那种
of an interesting guy but basically he
一个有趣的家伙，但基本上他
takes the radio signals which are
接收的无线电信号是
digital and streams that data out into a
数字化并将数据流传输到
file that can be visualized or what
可以可视化的文件或其他
we'll do is actually capture the output
我们要做的实际上是捕获输出
of 1090 and push it up to a Oracle IOT
1090并将其推升至Oracle IOT
node and one of the tools that we use is
节点，我们使用的工具之一是
called net cat it's been around forever
叫做网猫，它已经永远存在了
the tcp/ip Swiss Army knife you can use
您可以使用的tcp / ip瑞士军刀
net cat just about on any kind of
几乎任何种类的网猫
program so if you've got a computer that
程序，如果您有一台计算机
is transmitting some kind of data run
正在传输某种数据运行
net cat on it you can see what's going
网猫就可以了
across the wire you can take that data
可以在线获取数据
and throw it up to an IOT device and
并把它扔到物联网设备上
very easily you know
你很容易知道
now that's becomes another IOT device
现在这成为了另一个物联网设备
even if the device wasn't written for it
即使该设备不是为它编写的
dumped 1090 clearly wasn't written for
倾销1090显然不是为了
IOT was written to do one thing and
物联网被写做一件事，
that's to transmit your location to tell
就是要传达您的位置信息
you about where you are in the airplane
关于你在飞机上的位置
but but we're gonna use it to actually
但我们要用它来实际
capture data and stream it so another
捕获数据并将其流式传输
tool we use is IOT cloud service this
我们使用的工具是物联网云服务
comes in many different flavors it's
有很多不同的口味
almost a software-as-a-service product
几乎是软件即服务的产品
so if you look at their fleet management
所以如果你看他们的车队管理
and some of their other application
和其他一些应用
layers that they built on top of IOT
他们在物联网之上构建的层
we're using kind of a basic layer which
我们正在使用一种基本层
is the Oracle event hub which is
是Oracle事件中心
basically based on it's a Kafka it's a
基本上是基于卡夫卡
managed Kafka service and I think we
管理Kafka服务，我认为我们
talked a little bit about the components
谈到了一些组件
so to put this thing together we'll just
所以把这东西放在一起
I used a Raspberry Pi 3 that's that's
我用的是Raspberry Pi 3
one of the newer versions
较新的版本之一
they've even got some smaller ones but
他们甚至有一些较小的
we put the heatsinks on on this thing go
我们把散热器放在这东西上
ahead and install the antennas you want
提前安装所需的天线
to make sure that you match the antenna
确保您匹配天线
for the radio because
为了广播
you know that's that's gonna be you want
你知道那就是你想要的
to get the best signal you can get I've
得到最好的信号，你可以得到我
gotten on this one up to 70 miles away
骑到了这个距离不超过70英里的地方
so at this time I I had put a little
所以这个时候我已经放了一点
piece of paper to separate the two
一张纸将两者分开
pieces but the thing thing lights up it
碎片，但事物照亮了它
comes to life it's kind of it's kind of
充满生命，这是一种
cool you know you don't you don't see
酷，你知道你不，你没看到
that a lot and just pure software so I
这么多，只是纯软件，所以我
needed a case so I took this pizza box
需要一个箱子，所以我拿了这个披萨盒
and a battery and just taped everything
和电池，然后用胶带将所有东西录音
down and then ran the cables outside
向下然后将电缆放到外面
okay kind of see how we did it there and
好吧，看看我们是如何做到的，
then I took it flying and it worked so
然后我让它飞起来，所以效果很好
that was the first iteration a few years
那是几年来的第一次迭代
ago so what do we do next that that
以前，那么我们下一步该怎么做
application was reporting data locally I
应用程序正在本地报告数据
was visualizing on this this application
正在对此应用程序进行可视化
here called for flight you're welcome to
这里欢迎您的光临
come take a look at it so told me where
来看看吧，所以告诉我在哪里
I was and what other planes were around
我当时和周围还有其他飞机
me so that was great but now I want to
我，那太好了，但现在我想
get the data off of this thing and
从这件事中得到数据
stream it to the IOT cloud so what I'm
流到物联网云，所以我
gonna do is find the process and the
要做的就是找到流程，
port that dump 10 90s running on and
转储运行10 90的端口，
then run netcat in this case there's a
然后在这种情况下运行netcat
derivative called Kafka cat that will
称为卡夫卡猫的衍生物
take the output of that port and push it
获取该端口的输出并将其推入
to the Oracle event hub if you don't
如果您不这样做，请转到Oracle事件中心
want to use Oracle event hub you can use
想要使用可以使用的Oracle事件中心
Kafka or a really nice derivative of
Kafka或一个很好的衍生品
Kafka called confluent which gives you
卡夫卡称为汇合，这给你
some database features and allows you to
一些数据库功能，并允许您
store you know virtually infinite data
存储几乎无限的数据
so you can come back later and get to it
所以你可以稍后再来
it also gives you a REST API to query
它还为您提供了一个REST API进行查询
that data and apply some schema to it
该数据并对其应用一些模式
because otherwise it'd be pretty much
因为否则会差不多
schema-less
无模式
basically what we do is Kafka cat
基本上我们要做的就是卡夫卡猫
becomes the producer of data it produces
成为它产生的数据的产生者
data on what we call a topic and then
有关我们称为主题的数据，然后
that goes into confluence or the Oracle
融合或甲骨文
event hub
活动中心
and to get it into the Oracle database
并将其放入Oracle数据库
we're using Oracle database as a service
我们正在使用Oracle数据库作为服务
which is another Oracle cloud product
这是另一个Oracle云产品
and it allows you to store both schema
它允许您存储两个模式
tables as in the traditional sense of a
传统意义上的桌子
relational database but we can also
关系数据库，但我们也可以
store Jason or schema-less documents and
存储Jason或无模式文档，以及
we use an adapter called coffin connect
我们使用一个称为棺材连接的适配器
and we push data to this database
然后将数据推送到该数据库
through JDBC and then on top of all this
通过JDBC，然后最重要的是
we built an application that basically
我们构建了一个基本上
is html5 and JavaScript and we use the
是html5和JavaScript，我们使用
Java Script Google Maps API to visualize
Java Script Google Maps API可视化
the aircraft locations here's kind of
飞机在这里的位置
what if you do netcat on the data this
如果您对数据执行netcat怎么办
is kind of what the raw data looks like
有点像原始数据
they come streaming out I've gotten up
他们流了出来，我起床了
to 300 rows a second from this thing so
从这个东西到每秒300行
it can stream quite a bit of data with
它可以用
very my new aircraft positions or you
我的新飞机职位还是你
can kind of chunk it down so it doesn't
可以将它切成块，这样就不会
stream as much but that's kind of the
流一样多，但这有点
nature of things as as we switch from
当我们从
kind of a batch program to a streaming
一种批处理程序流
program we're going to be ingesting all
程序，我们将吸收所有
of these streams and later we will apply
这些流中，稍后我们将应用
some schema types to them so here here's
他们的一些模式类型，所以这里是
an image of kind of what the record
某种记录的图像
types look like what those fields mean
类型看起来像那些字段的意思
you know we have aircraft idea IDs hex
你知道我们的飞机想法ID是十六进制的
hexadecimal identifier altitude latitude
十六进制标识符海拔纬度
longitude you know any specific alerts
经度，您知道任何特定的警报
or emergencies and then there's even one
或紧急情况，甚至有一个
that basically tells you if the
基本上可以告诉您
aircrafts on the ground by this is just
地面上的飞机只是
another vision of what you can do with
您可以做什么的另一种看法
Kafka you've got these producers you can
卡夫卡，你有这些生产商，你可以
stream data to multiple nodes on
将数据流传输到上的多个节点
multiple availability zones and you can
多个可用区，您可以
consume it when you want to so the first
想要的时候先食用它
one is we go into the demo so since
一个是我们进入演示，因此
we're not getting any signal on this one
我们对此没有任何信号
I'll just show you real quick what the
我将很快向您展示
producer and the consumer look like
生产者和消费者看起来像
so there's some data that I streamed let
所以我流了一些数据
me go let me zoom in here sorry guys
我去让我放大这里对不起
hmm
嗯
okay this a little bit better
好吧，这好一点了
I need my mouse back anything
我需要鼠标退回任何东西
oops they didn't like that sorry
哎呀，他们不喜欢那对不起
now I wish I hadn't done that I still
现在我希望我没有做，我仍然
have it
有它
a spinning beach ball of death here
一个旋转的沙滩死亡球
looks like it's coming up
看起来好像要来了
this is play music these are actual
这是播放音乐，这些是实际的
good God okay I'm going to I can see my
天哪，好吧，我要去看我的
screen here so let me just gather these
屏幕在这里，所以让我收集这些
windows and sorry about that
Windows，对此感到抱歉
okay let's on
好吧，让我们继续
all right so let me I'll just zoom in
好吧，让我放大
okay so here we go
好吧，我们开始
actually don't play a song Jeff don't do
实际上不播放杰夫不喜欢的歌曲
that the song that he has on there is
他的那首歌是
down down down down down okay well sorry
下来下来下来很好抱歉
few minutes yeah I don't want to mess
几分钟，是的，我不想弄乱
with it anymore but I'll zoom in here in
有了它，但我会在这里放大
a second okay
第二好
well anyways I had done this previously
好吧，我之前已经做到了
so here's what that data stream looks
所以这是数据流的样子
like so these messages come from Kafka
像这样，这些消息来自卡夫卡
and then what we can do the raspberry pi
然后我们可以做什么树莓派
will actually push those messages on
实际上将这些消息推送到
there and so this is what that looks
在那里，这就是看起来
like so we've got you know producer and
就像这样，我们让您知道制作人和
let me see if I can go in here
让我看看我是否可以进去
so ad SB is also a mesh network but only
因此广告SB也是网状网络，但仅
if you've got there's two versions of it
如果您有两个版本
there's a dsb in and then there's a dsb
里面有一个dsb，然后有一个dsb
out only really modern aircraft are
只有真正的现代飞机
equipped with a DSP out but in one year
配备了DSP，但在一年内
they'll all be mandated to do that so
他们都将被授权这样做
they do relate ship to ship information
他们确实将船与船信息联系起来
from the ground station and the ground
从地面站和地面
station is responsible for picking up
车站负责接载
weather as well and the weather the
天气以及
digital weather information is broadcast
广播数字天气信息
over something called T's B and that is
在所谓的T的B上
also relayed from ship to ship yeah you
也从船到船转播是的，你
can see better and at the end I'll show
可以看得更好，最后我将展示
you a kind of a a crowd-sourced solution
您是一种众包解决方案
where you can collaborate with other
在这里您可以与其他人合作
people that do Raspberry Pi as well so
也有做Raspberry Pi的人
anyways we got producers and consumers
无论如何，我们得到了生产者和消费者
that's what I was trying to show you
那就是我想告诉你的
about that I apologize let's just stick
关于我的道歉，让我们坚持一下
to the slides and then the demo so and
幻灯片，然后演示
slide show
幻灯片放映
and so basically we use this Kafka Avro
所以基本上我们使用这个Kafka Avro
console producer and consumer commands
控制台生产者和使用者命令
and this is kind of what the database
这就是数据库
looks like and what a message sample
看起来像什么，消息样本
looks like coming out of the Raspberry
看起来像从树莓出来
Pi above a wet oh I got you
Pi湿透了，我明白了
well those are so those are in feet and
好吧，那些都在脚下，
that is universal in aviation and the
在航空业和
speed is given in nautical miles and
速度以海里为单位
nautical miles are based on the
海里是基于
circumference of the earth so yep that's
是地球的周长
a good question the u.s. introduced a
一个很好的问题，我们介绍了一个
normal system and then you introduced
普通系统，然后您介绍了
they don't call it a quarter pounder
他们不称它为四分之一磅
with cheese over there all right so
那里的奶酪好吧
we're moving so iot-cloud again this
我们再次移动了物联网云
allows you to do this in a graphical way
允许您以图形方式执行此操作
versus the way I try to show you you can
与我尝试向您展示的方式
explore the streams and give the demo so
探索溪流并进行演示
I'll just want to show you the
我只想告诉你
application that we've built and so you
我们构建的应用程序，因此您
can see this is written in Oracle apex
可以看到这是用Oracle apex编写的
has anybody used Oracle apex yep
有没有人使用过Oracle apex是的
all right so Oracle a for that simple
好的，Oracle就这么简单
these extremely simple to use yes so low
这些非常简单易用，是那么低
code development platform
代码开发平台
and I want to run fly tracker
我想运行飞行追踪器
okay let me login
好吧，让我登录
all right so I login I want to watch all
好的，所以我登录后我想看全部
of these okay and so this is just the
这些还可以，所以这仅仅是
last data set I've got the refresh said
我刷新的最后一个数据集说
- hi
-嗨
so that's you if you were up in the air
如果你在空中，那就是你
this afternoon
今天下午
it's basically that's I'm sorry this
基本上是对不起
thing's trying to but basically that's
事情正在努力，但基本上那是
it my planes okay there we go okay so as
我的飞机还可以吗
I've showing you the track and the
我给你看了曲目和
orientation and it's moving the aircraft
方向，它正在移动飞机
so this is some data that we recorded
这是我们记录的一些数据
earlier a little chunky the data because
早些时候将数据大块
I had trouble seeing through some of the
我很难看清某些
buildings but that's kind of the idea
建筑，但这是个主意
and that network is extremely slow
而且网络非常慢
that's basically the demo and if you
基本上就是演示，如果您
want to see kind of the code it's really
想要看到真正的代码
simple there's one page to this
很简单，只有一页
application or there's two pages a login
应用程序或两个页面登录
page and then this page sorry the
页面，然后此页面对不起
network's a little slow here and if I go
网络在这里有点慢，如果我去
to the map region blows up and make this
到地图区域爆炸并使其
bigger so basically you just set up the
更大，所以基本上您只需设置
initialize the map all right
初始化地图好
create map and this is a neat function
创建地图，这是一个整洁的功能
here this is plot all flight paths and
这是绘制所有飞行路线和
this is user defined JavaScript function
这是用户定义的JavaScript函数
and this plots a single flight path and
这会绘制一条飞行路线，
that's for if we only want to plot a
这是因为如果我们只想绘制一个
single plane and then this one plots all
一架飞机，然后这一个图全部
the flight paths and this is just a
飞行路线，这只是一个
straight out of the textbook Google Maps
直接从教科书Google地图
API okay
API没问题
let me do this
我来做
let me turn it back over where we're
让我把它转回去
going next turn it back over to oh yeah
接下来要把它转回哦，是的
any useful use cases so I did look on
任何有用的用例，所以我确实在
the internet and I found there's a lot
上网，我发现有很多东西
of people that have put their toaster
放烤面包机的人
in IOT they've both done it as makers
在物联网中，他们都作为制造商做到了
and they actually have productized this
他们实际上已经生产了这个
solution but I was looking for some
解决方案，但我一直在寻找一些
real-world use cases of course the
当然，现实中的用例
obvious one is air traffic control it's
显而易见的是空中交通管制
already in used collision avoidance for
已经用于避免碰撞
example but you know you might use it to
示例，但您知道您可能会用它来
survey a competitor maybe a Gordon Gekko
调查竞争对手，也许是戈登·格科（Gordon Gekko）
is flying to you know Erie Pennsylvania
飞往你知道宾夕法尼亚州的伊利
to buy anacott steel and you want to you
买阿纳科特钢铁，你想要你
want to know where he's going
想知道他要去哪里
that would be a really easy thing to do
那将是一件非常容易的事情
you can crowdsource a worldwide tracking
您可以众包全球追踪
system if you get a bunch of these and
系统，如果您有一堆这些和
get people to participate and that's
让人们参与，那就是
actually been done so I'll show you how
实际上已经完成，所以我将向您展示
to tie into that later curiosity maybe
为了以后的好奇心
you live near an airport and you always
你住在机场附近，你总是
wondered where that planes going maybe
想知道飞机可能去哪里
the you know the Airbus a380 a huge
你知道空中客车A380巨大
thing right it's just flying over I was
没错，那只是飞过我
like hey were they going fleet tracking
就像他们要去追踪舰队一样
so we're where is my fleet and I
所以我们在我的舰队在哪里
actually had an interesting use case
实际上有一个有趣的用例
from a cargo company they wanted to know
来自他们想知道的货运公司
when the plane was on the ground because
当飞机在地面上时
for some reason they didn't you know it
由于某种原因，他们不知道
wasn't their planes it was different
不是他们的飞机吗？
planes and they were always scheduled
飞机，他们总是被安排
differently so they want to know when
不同，所以他们想知道什么时候
that plane hit was touched down so they
那架飞机被击中了，所以他们
could mobilize and they had no way to do
可以动员，他们无能为力
that reliably this would be $100 way to
可靠地，这将是100美元
do that event correlation the tax man
做那个事件关联税务员
here in California you know you guys
在加利福尼亚，你知道你们
have a lot of taxes so you know use tax
有很多税，所以你知道使用税
you have a very expensive airplane ten
你有一架非常昂贵的飞机十
million dollars you might want to know
您可能想知道的一百万美元
where when that airplane is is using
那架飞机在哪里使用
your your county and asset valuation so
您的县和资产评估，所以
used airplanes have different values
二手飞机有不同的价值
based on usage if planes just sitting
根据使用情况（如果只是坐飞机）
there rusting it's gonna really affect
生锈会真正影响
its value okay so crowdsource aircraft
它的价值还行，所以众包飞机
tracking so flight aware is I don't know
跟踪，所以我不知道飞行
if you've used it it tells you gain in
如果您使用过它，它会告诉您获得收益
four
四
but also where planes are it uses
而且飞机在哪里使用
exactly this technology as part of its
正是这项技术的一部分
system and if you connect the Raspberry
系统，如果您连接了Raspberry
Pi if you build one of these in
Pi，如果您在其中构建其中之一
connected you actually get their
连接你实际上得到他们的
enterprise $90 a month solution for free
企业每月90美元的免费解决方案
so now you can have an API that you can
所以现在您可以拥有一个API
interrogate that's worldwide to your
向您的全球询问
point earlier and that's for free so you
早点，这是免费的，所以你
can write API calls and build
可以编写API调用并进行构建
applications on top of FlightAware just
仅在FlightAware上的应用程序
because you've connected a single
因为您已经连接了一个
Raspberry Pi to their network let me
树莓派到他们的网络让我
turn it around to rich he's going to
把它变成富有，他要
talk about where to take this in the
谈论在哪里拿这个
future I don't know where you guys will
未来我不知道你们会在哪里
take it in the future to tell you the
以后再告诉你
truth
真相
but it's I mean it's up to you how many
但这是我的意思，这取决于你
people ever watched Twilight Zone
人们曾经看过暮光区
you watch it today I'm telling you half
你今天看，我告诉你一半
of the Twilight zones there already
已经有暮光区
happened or you can see them in
发生了，或者您可以看到它们
development so right now is the time but
发展，现在是时候了，但是
why and this is the reason why why
为什么，这就是为什么
because when you look at something like
因为当你看着像
8-bit that's 2 times 2 times 2 times 2 8
8位，即2倍2倍2倍2 8
times its 256 you know back then when I
乘以它的256，那时候我就知道了
was playing video games you know get to
在玩你知道的视频游戏
scream 255 on pac-man what happens
在pac-man上尖叫255会发生什么
screen splits buffer overflow it's too
屏幕拆分缓冲区溢出也是
high so we got the 16-bit and what
高，所以我们得到了16位
happened we got Windows because people
碰巧我们有了Windows，因为人们
could put more code that was addressable
可以放置更多可寻址的代码
or memory this is the amount of memory
或内存，这是内存量
that's addressable for each of those
对于每个人来说都是可以解决的
32-bit 4 gig now if you happen to put a
如果您碰巧将一个32位4演出
sign like use one of those 32 bits for a
像使用32位中的一个
plus or a minus instead of 4 gig you
加号或减号，而不是4个演出
only a 2 gig just to let you know which
仅2个演出就让您知道
some people do but 4 gig what did we get
有些人做，但是4演出我们得到了什么
when it when when a hit kind of
当它什么时候当一种打击
mainstream 32 bit got the Internet I put
主流32位上网我放
it in miles per hour
每小时英里
windows was one mile an hour the
窗户每小时一英里
internet was 65,000 miles an hour
互联网是每小时65,000英里
looking at it bit by bit 64 bit the jump
一点一点地看着它64位跳跃
were making now were you starting to see
现在正在制作，您开始看到
more robotics you're starting to see
您将开始看到更多的机器人技术
stuff like IOT
物联网之类的东西
you're gonna invent some I'm sure give
你会发明一些我肯定会给的
me a Jerry a few shares don't forget
我一个杰里几股不要忘记
about us 300 trillion miles an hour
大约每小时300万亿英里
you're gonna see a robotics I mean it's
你会看到一个机器人，我的意思是
gonna be substantially different and
将会大不相同，
then after that 64-bit - 128-bit five
然后是64位-128位5
trillion trillion billion miles per hour
每小时兆兆兆英里
it's gonna see implants and mass I mean
我会说植入物和质量
let's look at those numbers again it's
让我们再看看那些数字
just the way it jumps you know god I'll
只是跳跃的方式，你知道我会的
be obviously wanted things just start
显然想要事情才开始
going fast right now so you've hit the
现在进展很快，所以您已经
right place at the right point in time
在正确的时间点正确的地方
you're literally in the right place
你真的在正确的地方
start leveraging this technology 2015
开始利用这项技术2015
wasn't all about tech anymore all the
不再是所有关于技术的问题了
sudden was all about robotics human
突然间，关于机器人的一切
augmentation you know building your home
您知道的扩建房屋
to be connected
被连接
that's what became big you know you go
那就是变大的你知道你去了
to Honda a robot takes you to your
到本田，机器人将您带到
meeting pour you a cup of coffee along
见面会一起倒一杯咖啡
the way they don't have this yet but I
他们还没有这个的方式，但是我
figured in the future you know you go to
想着以后你知道你会去
a company they're probably gonna have
他们可能会拥有的公司
this da Vinci Surgical System I don't
我没有这个达芬奇手术系统
know what it was ten twenty million
知道那是一两千万
dollars only they're gonna be like you
美元，只有他们会像你一样
know on the way to the meeting you want
知道您要开会的方式
to get that appendix out you know you're
找出那个附录，你知道
showing some sense or some pain there
在那儿表现出某种感觉或某种痛苦
we'll just pull that out on the way
我们将其删除
we'll just carry your deer meeting how
我们会随身携带您的鹿见面会
about that available now all of these
关于现在可用的所有这些
things they're already there so what's
他们已经在那里的东西，那是什么
the hype cycle in 27th 2016 2017 won't
2016年27日的炒作周期不会
come until 2018 but it's all about
到2018年为止
implants you know human augmentation
你知道人类植入的植入物
taking prosthetics and starting to
接受假肢并开始
augment them so they could put them
增强他们，以便他们可以把它们
inside you taking computers at
在你的电脑里
nanotechnology putting it inside your
纳米技术将其放入您的
bloodstream so you can wirelessly
血液，因此您可以无线
communicate with stuff Larry Ellison
与Larry Ellison交流
invested in a company where you take the
投资一家公司
pill and it can tell you what you ate
药丸，它可以告诉你吃什么
tell you exactly what's in your stomach
告诉你肚子里到底是什么东西
it's there today
今天在那里
you know it's instead of Instagram it's
你知道这不是Instagram，而是
going to be just implant you know the
只是植入，你知道
picture is gonna pop into your head I
图片会突然出现在你的头上
guess this device down here at the
猜这个设备在这里
bottom this is one Israeli company
底部，这是一家以色列公司
it's in your bloodstream you know you
在你的血液里，你知道你
spin that little dial based on your
根据您的要求旋转小转盘
blood flowing and it will power devices
血液流动，它将为设备供电
you know so if we're in the middle of
你知道吗，如果我们在
the desert you know you can use that or
您知道可以使用的沙漠或
you can use it here
你可以在这里使用
I think I'll plug it in myself they're
我想我会自己插入
already implanting into the brain it's
已经植入大脑了
already happening now here's a mouse
已经发生了，现在有只老鼠
they put some implants in and it runs a
他们放了一些植入物，然后运行
more complex maze works today
今天更复杂的迷宫作品
here's a lady uses a robotic arm to get
这是一位女士用机械臂
a drink it's there today because of
今天因为那里有饮料
128-bit and 256-bit which is about 1/2
128位和256位，约为1/2
of Google if you know what at Google is
如果您知道Google的职责是
goog ol1 with a hundred zeros on it with
Goog ol1上有一百个零
256 bit you're gonna get about 1/2 of
256位您将获得大约1/2的
Google but they say that you'll 2045 you
Google，但他们说您2045年就可以了
know it'll be that point where you will
知道那将是你将要去的那一点
transcend biology you know if you cut
超越生物学，你知道如果你削减
off your arm is it still you if I get a
离开你的手臂，如果我得到
prosthetic is it still me what do you
义肢是我还是你
think who says yes who says no ok what
想想谁说是谁说不可以
if I get a new heart people would get a
如果我有了新的心，人就会得到
heart transplant in the beginning people
心脏移植开始的人们
were not sure it was gonna be them when
不知道什么时候会成为他们
they woke up what if they could 3d print
他们醒来了，如果可以3D打印
with my own cells a kidney they've
用我自己的细胞，肾脏，
already done it with them with mice is
已经和老鼠一起做过
it still me people are working on
人们还是在努力
whether they can print your face when
他们是否可以在什么时候打印你的脸
you were 30 years old and burn off skin
你今年30岁，烧掉了皮肤
and print on a 30 year old don't laugh
并在30岁的孩子上打印不要笑
it's happening right now they're working
现在正在工作
on it so what happens when you can go
因此，当您可以去时会发生什么
into my brain and print everything
进入我的大脑并打印所有内容
that's in there and I print a clone and
在那里，我打印了一个克隆，
he knows everything in me obviously we
他知道我内心的一切，显然我们
split at that point into two different
在那个时候分为两个不同的
thing is it still me anymore who says
难道我仍然是谁
it's told me now anyone because that's
现在有人告诉我，因为那是
what's gonna happen when you hit 2045
当您达到2045时会发生什么
you're saying it will absolutely be
你是说那绝对是
possible we'll start to hit this where
可能我们会在这里开始
you're transcending biology they call it
你超越生物学他们称之为
this singularity if you've ever read
如果你读过这种奇点
very Kurzweil stuff it's the guy who
非常Kurzweil的东西是那个家伙
invented the reader for blind people
为盲人发明了读者
it's one of his inventions
这是他的发明之一
but it's that moment in technology where
但这是技术的那一刻
things go so fast that there's a rupture
事情进展得如此之快以至于破裂
in literally human beings they can't
在人类中，他们不能
handle it anymore and they say that
处理了，他们说
point is gonna happen in 2045 there's
关键会在2045年发生
not many things that go on time that
没有那么多的事情可以按时进行
they say this is coming in the future
他们说这会在未来
that I haven't seen in my lifetime
我一生中从未见过的
downside is security anyone see goes to
缺点是任何人都可以看到的安全性
the show this used to be a cartoon
表演这曾经是卡通
anyone see the Japanese cartoon ghost in
有人在里面看到日本卡通鬼
the show came out in the 80s it's very
该节目是在80年代问世的
good just to let you know but it's about
很好，只是让您知道，但这是关于
hackers that will hack into your mind
黑客会侵入您的脑海
you know and how to prevent that you
你知道如何防止你
know right now we're just hacking into
知道现在我们正在入侵
Equifax well as you build implants
当您制作植入物时，Equifax会很好
somebody's gonna figure out how to do
有人会想办法
that I like this one I tweeted this a
我喜欢这个，我发了一条推文
little while ago but it's like you know
不久前，但这就像你知道的
hackers 30 bucks in Bitcoin or the next
黑客在比特币或下一个30美元
time I smell smoke I just might let you
时间我闻到烟味我可能会让你
sleep sorry you know this is the
睡觉对不起，你知道这是
internet of ransomware of things your
物联网勒索软件
Roomba is like you know why were my
Roomba就像你知道为什么是我的
hacker some money or I'm gonna blow dirt
黑客一些钱，否则我会被污垢吹走
all over this place how long will it be
整个地方要多久
till that happens until they lock your
直到那件事发生，直到他们锁定您的
refrigerators a little lock you out of
冰箱让您无法入内
your car starting to happen how do you
你的车开始发生你如何
be competitive in the future and the
在未来和
answer is any great technology you're
答案是您拥有的任何伟大技术
not gonna beat robots in AI and the
不会击败AI和
answer is you're going to be the guy
答案是你要成为那个家伙
implanting things to compete with that
植入东西与之竞争
robot
机器人
Cyberdyne systems oh that's an
Cyber​​dyne系统哦，这是
interesting name built a Hal suit that
有趣的名字建立了一个Hal西装
makes you much stronger if you can't
如果你做不到，会让你更坚强
walk you're able to walk you've seen
走，你就能走，你已经看到
obviously Apple watch virtual reality
显然，Apple Watch虚拟现实
but the goal is going to be to start
但目标是要开始
implanting things in you so that you can
将东西植入您体内，以便您可以
compete with those robotics final
与那些机器人决赛竞争
thoughts anyone remembers Star Trek
任何人都记得星际迷航的想法
didn't it look futuristic way back one I
难道不是我未来的方式吗？
mean look at that phone they're using
看看他们正在使用的手机
what if you put out a phone today that
如果今天你放电话怎么办
look like this people would laugh you
看起来这个人会笑你
out
出
the business what is that ancient thing
这个生意是什么古老的东西
where'd you get that ancient Egypt
你从哪里得到那古老的埃及
things are accelerating tremendously
事情正在大大加速
ghost in the shell' people who those
壳中的幽灵'那些人
used things of the world its passing
用过世界的事物
away ghost in the shell' is about even
消失在壳中的幽灵'甚至
networking different minds together you
将不同的思想联系在一起
know you're you're kind of networked in
知道你在网络中
this room right now but they're gonna
现在这个房间，但是他们要
physically do it in the future some
在将来实际进行
people think you know that's impossible
人们认为你知道那是不可能的
I always say nothing's impossible when I
我总是说什么都不是不可能
came here twenty years ago I had to go
二十年前来到这里我不得不去
to a company event it was raining I
在公司活动中下雨了
thought it's impossible to get a cab
以为不可能坐出租车
this is before the days of uber and all
这是在uber和所有时代之前
that and right then a cab went by and I
那然后一辆出租车过去了，我
was like taxi and it just kept going
就像出租车，而且一直在行驶
I like taxi I can't believe it
我喜欢出租车，我简直不敢相信
one went by and he won't stop there was
一个人过去了，他不会停在那里
a red light so I ran up there and I
红灯，所以我跑到那里，我
looked in the window I'm like taxi
看着窗户，我就像出租车
and he's like all right he goes where
就像他没事的一样
are you going and I told him he goes
你要去吗，我告诉他他要去
alright I'll take you I was like sorry
好吧，我带你，我很抱歉
to put him out I mean he maybe was
把他赶出去我的意思是他也许是
off-duty I don't know so then he takes
下班我不知道，所以他带
me there and I'm like how much is it and
我在那里，我想多少钱，
he's like noticed there's no meter and
他就像注意到那里没有仪表，
I'm like wow there's no meter why is
我就像哇，为什么没有仪表
that
那
and he goes cuz I'm a pizza delivery guy
他去找我是披萨送货员
and it looked like a cab because they
而且看起来像出租车，因为他们
had like the thing on it and I said well
喜欢上面的东西，我说很好
why did you take me he said you were
你为什么要带我他说你是
just so insistent and so how you gonna
如此坚持，所以你要如何
create the future you you have to
创造未来，你必须
believe you can do those impossible
相信你可以做那些不可能的事情
things
东西
now we go for Jerry well that's it I
现在我们去杰里好了，就是我
hope we covered kind of what you were
希望我们能介绍您的情况
looking for again let me close with this
再次寻找让我结束这个
quote things may come to those who wait
引述那些可能会等待的人
but only things left by those who hustle
但只有那些忙碌的人留下的东西
Abraham Lincoln again hello at viscosity
亚伯拉罕·林肯再次打招呼
na komm if you want the book Julio much
na komm，如果您想更喜欢Julio这本书
she coddled
她拥抱
the first warning you get your first
第一个警告，你得到第一个
pick one of those three
选择这三个之一
Peter Erikson air traffic control
彼得·埃里克森（Peter Erikson）空中交通管制
systems I'll see if he's here he's got
系统，我看看他是否在这里
to be here that's him
来这里就是他
Richard go this one this one's already
理查德去这个这个已经
got a song on it it includes a chip take
上面有一首歌，里面有筹码
whatever you want it's all yours
无论您想要什么，都属于您
no one's ready to go and everyone else
没有人准备出发，其他所有人
one candy so you can come and get some
一个糖果，所以你可以来拿一些
candy so thanks for coming have a great
糖果，谢谢你的光临
day
天
[Applause]
[掌声]